SRUSHTI RAUT

srushtir25@gmail.com | 0091 9773243734 Mumbai, 400042 India

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/srushtiraut



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven Business Development Executive with career history in multi-state distributed businesses and proven skill in marketing, organizing and client relations. Motivating leader with strengths in building strategic relationships to support key business initiatives. Highly skilled in change management. Offering excellent interpersonal and communication skills and experience managing matrixed organizations.

SKILLS

- Order management
- Relationship building and rapport
- Cash-flow analysis
- Financial operations
- Sales Pipeline Management
- Revenue and Profit Maximization
- Prospect Targeting
- Corporate Budgeting
- Consultative Sales Techniques

- Client Relations
- Product and Service Sales
- Goals and Performance
- Business Development and Planning
- Brand Management
- Brand Marketing
- Market Research
- Social Media Manager
- Marketing Campaigns & Management

WORK HISTORY

Business Development Executive | Susema Pvt. Ltd - Mumbai, India

02/2021 - Current

- Defined and integrated roles, responsibilities and processes for business team and data management organization
- Led cross-functional teams to create impactful messaging, demand-generation programs and sales tools
- Identified potential prospects for sale using ATL methodologies resulting into 33% increase in sales growth quarterly
- Developed and implemented value-added strategies to increase profitability, expand market share and cement customer relationships
- Created strategic and tactical sales initiatives for forward planning to meet key objectives
- Enhanced marketing exposure through successful website content management and direct correspondence with potential clients
- Collaborated with sales and marketing departments to support business objectives and client acquisition

Marketing Executive | Veena World Tourism Limited - Mumbai, India

02/2020 - 02/2021

- Facilitated the reach of the brand, increase customer engagement and brand recognition
- Developed and designed in house changes for better customer service
- Developed and executed marketing programs and general business solutions resulting in increased company exposure, customer traffic and elevated sales numbers
- Conducted research-based work to understand the customer requirements leading to modification in sales strategy and implementing new marketing activities along with new product
- Designed promotional plans, accomplished digital marketing to attract the customers through innovative advertisements and literatures
- Created and deployed successful strategies underpinning significant growth in Tourism areas
- Developed innovative and targeted collateral to support overall branding objectives

Marketing manager | COABARC - Amaravati, India

05/2019 - 07/2019

- Carried out work as social media marketer with inventive and innovative solutions by organizing webinars, events for promotion of student work, creating animated advertisements and promotion of the same through paid advertisements leading to increase in footfall of admissions
- Facilitated the team to increase the brand, increase customer engagement and achieved brand recognition
- Capitalized on industry and marketplace trends to strategize marketing solutions and enhance business operations
- Executed optimal sales strategies to achieve commercial goals for target market

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Certified Digital Marketer.
- Participated in the workshop and seminars for new age of marketing, 2019.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Digital Marketer
- New Age of Marketing Seminar attended

EDUCATION

University of Pune - India 05/2020

Master in Business Administration: Marketing

University of Mumbai - India 05/2017

Master of Science: Biotechnology

University of Mumbai - India 05/2015

Bachelor of Science: Biotechnology

LANGUAGES

Marathi, Hindi: Native language

English: C2 German: A2